First, there was
the collapse of civilization:
Anarchy, genocide, starvation.
Then, when it seemed
things couldn't get any worse...
We got the plague
the living death...
Quickly closing its fist
over the entire planet.
And then we heard the rumors...
That the last scientists
were working on a cure...
That would end the plague
and restore the world.
Restore it? Why?
I like the death.
I like the misery!
I like this world!
Come on, Pearl! It's clear.
I think we lost Fender and his pirates.
We've got a chance to reach
the Prox township and hire a slinger.
Get... get going, Pearl.
I'll try to hold them here.
Find a slinger to help you, Pearl.
Now!
Get her.
- Let her go!
- To Atlanta?
To cure the plague
with the information she has.
I wanna own it.
Own the cure?
I'd be a god!
- But the misery could be stopped.
- I like the misery.
- The world could be changed.
- I like this world.
Go to hell!
Been there.
Thanks.
Wait!
Who are you?
Why did you help me?
I thought it was somebody else.
I can trust you.
For what?
To get me back to Atlanta.
There's a group of doctors there,
the last ones.
They've been working
on a cure for the plague.
They need information I have.
I swear it's the truth.
I'm a cyborg.
They created me to retrieve data from
the computer system here in the city.
Slinger!
That slinger can't help you now.
I'll take you to Atlanta...
And you'll give me the cure.
And if you don't...
I'll give you the horror show.
Get me back to Atlanta.
There's a group of doctors there,
the last ones.
They've been working on a cure for the
plague. They need information I have.
You think we're gonna swim
all the way to Atlanta?
I... can't... swim...
Asshole! I hate the water!
Hey, I caught a nice fish here!
Aaagh!
Hoist anchor, mates!
We got us a skin-job to take to Atlanta!
Say your final goodbyes to your daddy...
And let's be on our way.
I'm losing money. Let's go.
I don't know if I really trust you.
I don't know if there's really
any difference between slingers...
And the pirates that killed my pa.
But I guess I ain't got no choice.
You're the only guy that answered
the posting for the pay.
Just get us out of this city.
It's what I do.
Get people out of the city.
Let's go.
You're good with them.
I like them.
- It's beautiful.
- We'll be safe here.
Um...
Are you looking for that woman?
I heard the pirates say
she has a cure for the plague.
They're taking her to Atlanta.
Atlanta.
The pirates wanted a boat.
All this for a stupid boat.
Why are you still alive?
I hid when they came.
I saw them setting off
down the waterway to Charleston.
I was just getting ready to take off
when you showed up.
I figured you for one of the pirates.
I'm gone.
So, are you going after
that woman with the cure?
To save her from the pirates?
I'd like to help.
My family died from the plague.
So did most everybody else I've known.
So as soon as I heard the pirates
talk about this woman...
I knew I had to do something to help.
Keep moving.
You don't want my help?
- No.
- Think you can rescue her by yourself?
It's not my business.
You're not gonna try to save this woman?
You don't care?
Well, what do you care about?
Fender
there's a cure for the plague
and you don't give a shit?
What kind of jerk are you?
- Why don't you rescue her?
- Maybe I will.
You know, the short cut
to Charleston's a free road.
You can't stop me from traveling.
Good luck!
Not too much.
So do you think we'll find Fender?
We'll get him.
Tell me something.
I tried to kill you.
So why did you stay with me
while I was knocked out?
Sort of goes
against your hard-ass style.
It's because I felt sorry for you.
The man has a heart.
Fender's making his way down the
inter-coastal waterway to Charleston.
He stopped for wood
at hatteras yesterday.
Torched a settlement there.
I'll catch up with him.
Where the ocean meets
the road to Atlanta.
Folks generally make it a point
to stay out of Fender's path, gibs.
Not go looking to kill him.
I heard you'd given it up.
Found some peace in the country.
This is going to be our home.
You said you wanted a change.
Stay with us?
Just for a little while?
I was a fool, maze.
I started to believe in the dream.
Everybody's gotta have a dream,
gibs. A little hope.
Ha, look at old maze!
Got my bar, family.
How's that for hope?
Make sure you put your knives on
for the right reason, son.
What if you kill Fender? What then?
What about the rest of your life?
So the cure's not important, huh?
I got your ball!
Knock it off,
or I'll bash your brains out.
Hey!
I don't think this is yours.
Hey, kid.
Are you crazy?
This is the wasteland.
- We can't go through here.
- Fender has a boat. We're walking.
You want the cure. I want Fender.
Short cut to Charleston, my ass!
We are lost.
Typical.
Son of a bitch!
You're pretty good.
- Do you ever get used to it?
- Used to what?
The killing.
I didn't make this world.
Yeah, you only live in it.
Fender's boat will pass here.
Good.
Then we're stopping.
You're just a walking wound, aren't you?
Sorry-
I like scars, really.
So what did Fender do to you?
You know, if you let me help you...
You can help me.
No.
You still don't think
that woman is worth saving?
I don't want to see you die.
I don't wanna see you die either.
You're not gonna be here in the morning
when I wake up, are you?
It's ok.
What is it?
Fender
you were chosen because of
your matrix engineering background...
And the make-up of your personality.
You are the perfect choice
for this mission.
However, I think it's important...
That you understand
the ramifications of your decision.
I wouldn't have volunteered
if I didn't understand the consequences.
After the operation...
You will never
be the same again, Pearl.
The plague has destroyed so much.
We've lost our humanity.
We've lost our purpose.
There's no meaning in this world.
I wanna change that.
I'll bring back
the data you need.
I swear it.
Good luck, Pearl.
Don't worry, Pearl.
I'll get you to New York - and back.
We'll dock and reach
the inland road by noon.
Fender's boat.
Stay next to me.
Who are they?
Take 'em out.
Move!
- Wait here.
- I'm not gonna stay here!
I want you out of my way...
Until I see what's going on.
Look, I'm here to make sure
that woman lives.
And I'm not gonna let you do anything
that could hurt her.
Nothing's going to happen to her.
It's a promise.
A promise.
Fuck it!
Oh, shit.
Hyahh!
Fuck!
Come on!
Motherfucker!
I told my sister
that slingers kill pirates.
I'm gonna be a slinger some day.
No, you're not.
You'll do something better, Haley.
Go!
You, keep an eye on her.
Move!
Come on.
I'm not going with you. You're not
strong enough to get me to Atlanta.
Fender would eventually catch us.
Maybe kill me.
Certainly kill you.
Look, Fender must be destroyed.
In Atlanta, we have the means.
I'll lead him to his death.
Nothing can stop him in this world.
Not even you.
You!
You take her!
Here!
Over here!
- Can you make it?
- Yeah.
I guess I should have stayed put, huh?
Come on.
Let's go. Let's go.
Run! Run!
Stand him up!
Let's go.
Haley.
Haley!
What's wrong with you?
You're good with them.
I like them.
They like you, gibs.
This is going to be our home.
Stay with us?
Just for a little while?
It's up to you, honey.
If you can hold them, they'll live.
Fender!
I told you you were gonna need my help.
What's waiting in Atlanta?
What I told you.
The last of the old world.
What's waiting for me, cyborg?
Whatever you want.
Guns. Weapons.
The cure, if they find it.
Life.
Death.
Death?
You think you can stop me there.
No, we have a deal.
You'll fail.
Of course I would.
I know how strong you are.
Don't look down on me!
I don't.
Move!
Go!
No!
Come with me. Hurry!
I kill slingers!
Aaaaagh!
Stop m
stop m
please.
Nady!
- Fender!
- Fucker!
Hey, come on!
Fuck you!
Haley.
Welcome home, Pearl.
- Were you able to retrieve the data?
- Yes, I was.
Thanks to this man.
Stay with us, Gibson.
They need us out there. Let's go.
It's strange.
But I feel he's the real cure
for this world.
English - us - psdh